{
    "qna":[
        {
            "questionNumber":"q1",
            "question":"What is the pH value of H2O?",
            "answer":"7",
            "answerOptions":[
                "4",
                "7",
                "6"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q2",
            "question":"Acid turns blue litmus paper into which color?",
            "answer":"Red",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Red",
                "Green",
                "Black"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q3",
            "question":"Name the gland which is present above our kidneys?",
            "answer":"Adrenal",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Salivary",
                "Pituitary",
                "Adrenal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q4",
            "question":"What is the basic unit of our neural system?",
            "answer":"Neuron",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Neuron",
                "Nephron",
                "Proton"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q5",
            "question":"What is the unit of wavelength?",
            "answer":"Meter",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Diopter",
                "Hertz",
                "Meter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q6",
            "question":"Name the metal which is most ductile?",
            "answer":"Gold",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Gold",
                "Platinum",
                "Silver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q7",
            "question":"Name the part of the eye on which image is formed?",
            "answer":"Cornea",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Optic nerves",
                "Cornea",
                "Lens"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q8",
            "question":"Which device is used for measuring air pressure?",
            "answer":"Barometer",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Ammeter",
                "Barometer",
                "Voltmeter"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q9",
            "question":"What is the S.I unit of resistance?",
            "answer":"Ohm",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Volt",
                "Ampere",
                "Ohm"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q11",
            "question":"Name the process by which the human breathes?",
            "answer":"Respiration",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Digestion",
                "Respiration",
                "Photosynthesis"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q12",
            "question":"Name the part of the human body in which most of the digestion occurs?",
            "answer":"Small intestine",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Stomach",
                "Small intestine",
                "Large intestine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q13",
            "question":"Name the metal which is easily cut by a simple knife?",
            "answer":"Sodium",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Sodium",
                "Mercury",
                "Lead"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q14",
            "question":"Name the fabric which is used in making bulletproof jackets?",
            "answer":"Kevlar",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Iron",
                "Aluminium",
                "Kevlar"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q15",
            "question":"What is the scientific name of a mango?",
            "answer":"Mangifera indica",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Mangifera indica",
                "Homo sapiens",
                "Felis catus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q16",
            "question":"Who is the main producer of our ecosystem?",
            "answer":"Plants",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Bacteria",
                "Humans",
                "Plants"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q17",
            "question":"What is the symbol of gold?",
            "answer":"Au",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Au",
                "Hg",
                "Ag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q18",
            "question":"What is the symbol of gold?",
            "answer":"Au",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Au",
                "Hg",
                "Ag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q19",
            "question":"Which type of lens is used in microscope?",
            "answer":"Convex",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Concave",
                "Convex",
                "Cylindrical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNumber":"q20",
            "question":"What is the color of SO2 gas?",
            "answer":"Colorless",
            "answerOptions":[
                "Brown",
                "Black",
                "Colorless"
            ]
        }
    ]
}